<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Beniamino Green</title>
    <link>https://beniamino.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Beniamino Green</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://beniamino.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://beniamino.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 21:38:52 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://beniamino.org/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me I use this blog to write about my thoughts on quantitiative social science, programming, and causal inference.
Previously, I was an pre-doctoral fellow at the Yale Tobin Center for Economic Policy. Before this, I received a Master&amp;rsquo;s in Social Analysis and Research from Brown University, and a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s in Politics, Philosophy and Economics with a concentration in Quantitative Methods from the University College London.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The QUBT Quandry</title>
      <link>https://beniamino.org/post/2025-09-09-why-i-am-short-qubt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://beniamino.org/post/2025-09-09-why-i-am-short-qubt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quantum Computing Inc. (NASDAQ: QUBT) has soared to a $2.5 billion market cap
on the promise of “revolutionary” quantum breakthroughs. A closer look
suggests that its technology may be little more than smoke and mirrors. In this
report, I unpack how QUBT’s claims diverge from reality and why investors may
be badly mispricing the stock.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>January 2025 Jane Street Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://beniamino.org/post/2025-02-03-jane-street-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://beniamino.org/post/2025-02-03-jane-street-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;p&gt;Jane Street is a quantitative trading firm that puts out monthly puzzles. Last
month, I took a stab at their monthly puzzle, and share my solution in this post.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iceland Photos</title>
      <link>https://beniamino.org/post/2024-07-26-iceland-trip-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://beniamino.org/post/2024-07-26-iceland-trip-photos/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;p&gt;Photos from my recent trip to Iceland.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Haven Street Sweeping Tickets</title>
      <link>https://beniamino.org/post/2024-05-15-street-sweeping/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://beniamino.org/post/2024-05-15-street-sweeping/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;p&gt;I filed a FOIA request to obtain every street-sweeping ticket issued in New
Haven since 2021.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating R Plots without X11</title>
      <link>https://beniamino.org/post/2023-11-16-r-plots-without-x11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://beniamino.org/post/2023-11-16-r-plots-without-x11/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;p&gt;Cypress pros don’t want you to know about this one weird trick!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connecting to the Yale VPN on Linux</title>
      <link>https://beniamino.org/post/2023-11-05-using-yale-vpn-on-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://beniamino.org/post/2023-11-05-using-yale-vpn-on-linux/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;p&gt;A few hours ago, Yale changed the process of authenticating authenticating to
their VPN. If you were using the openconnect CLI, this might make it impossible
for you to sign in using the VPN. In this post, I show how to use the python
openconnect-sso package, which is a wrapper around openconnect, and will allow
you to use the new web-based SSO.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoomerjoin Featured on R-Weekly Podcast!</title>
      <link>https://beniamino.org/post/2023-10-11-zoomerjoin-feature/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://beniamino.org/post/2023-10-11-zoomerjoin-feature/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;p&gt;Listen to the podcast &lt;a href=&#34;https://rweekly.fireside.fm/139&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Thanks for the
shout out, guys!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Zoomerjoin</title>
      <link>https://beniamino.org/post/2023-10-05-introducing-zoomerjoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://beniamino.org/post/2023-10-05-introducing-zoomerjoin/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;p&gt;My new R package, Zoomerjoin, empowers you to fuzzily-join datasets at speeds
you never thought possible. Check out the article introducing the package in
the Journal of Open Source Software
&lt;a href=&#34;https://joss.theoj.org/papers/10.21105/joss.05693&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Don&#39;t Believe Mo Salah Reduced Hate Crimes</title>
      <link>https://beniamino.org/post/2023-07-26-i-don-t-believe-mo-salah-reduced-hate-crimes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://beniamino.org/post/2023-07-26-i-don-t-believe-mo-salah-reduced-hate-crimes/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;p&gt;I contest findings that Mo Salah signing with Liverpool F.C. reduced the number
of hate crimes in the area and decreased Islamophobia among Liverpool F.C.
Twitter followers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Entries in The Ben Green Style Guide</title>
      <link>https://beniamino.org/post/2023-07-24-new-entries-in-the-ben-green-style-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://beniamino.org/post/2023-07-24-new-entries-in-the-ben-green-style-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t say &amp;ldquo;control for&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;approaching significance&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Research Reproducible with &#39;GNU Make&#39;</title>
      <link>https://beniamino.org/post/2022-06-20-make-research-easy-with-make/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://beniamino.org/post/2022-06-20-make-research-easy-with-make/</guid>
      <description>GNU Make is a computer program long known to computer scientists, but tragically underused in the social sciences. Originally developed to manage the compilation of C/C++ code, Make can be used to automate running stages of your data analysis code whenever changes are made to the code that generates them. Using make will save time (code is run if and only if its dependencies are updated), eliminate a common class of errors (code is never run using old data or calculations), and free up your head space to write code rather than managing dependencies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://beniamino.org/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://beniamino.org/research/</guid>
      <description>Published Articles: Zoomerjoin: Superlatively Fast Fuzzy Joins: Researchers often have to link large datasets without access to a unique identifying key, or on the basis of a field that contains misspellings, small errors, or is otherwise inconsistent. Most popular methods to solve this problem involve comparing all possible pairs of matches between each dataset, incurring a computational cost proportional to the product of the rows in each dataset O(mn). As such, these methods do not scale to large datasets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software</title>
      <link>https://beniamino.org/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://beniamino.org/software/</guid>
      <description>Zoomerjoin zoomerjoin is an R package that empowers you to fuzzy-join massive datasets rapidly, and with little memory consumption. It is powered by high-performance implementations of Locality Sensitive Hashing, an algorithm that finds the matches records between two datasets without having to compare all possible pairs of observations. In practice, this means zoomerjoin can fuzzily-join datasets days, or even years faster than other matching packages. zoomerjoin has been used in-production to join datasets of hundreds of millions of names in a few hours.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
